<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Free Diamond</string>

    <string name="Details1">"Choosing a landing point is only the first step to victory.

Although it may seem trivial, it is not. Determining where to start allows you to decide whether to start the game correctly.

 The important thing is to choose a place that is isolated from other players, very close to the city, but not so close. So, the best option is to fall from the town, observe where other people fall and enter to explore.

 It is very important that we dont expose ourselves too much before we dont have the proper equipment, especially when we are everywhere where both quantity and quality are robbed, there will be players in many places."</string>
    <string name="Details2">"Once we land, the first thing we need to do is to find weapons, protection, first aid kits, etc.

At the beginning of the game, the best way is to grab everything we can find, because we can always improve and replace equipment."</string>
    <string name="Details3">"If there is no enemy in sight, it is a good idea to explore attractions such as watch towers, containers, battle es or military tents.

 In these places, whether it is weapons or supplies, there are usually a lot of loot.

 It is not very wise to explore these areas from the beginning, but if we do it in the middle of the game, there will always be a lot to do. There will definitely be fewer players lurking to destroy us.

 In such places, kits are usually found to improve bulletproof vests.

Please pay attention when exploring, because although you can wear a first-level vest, it is strongly recommended that you upgrade it as soon as possible.

The last player will always have powerful weapons."</string>
    <string name="Details4">"The safe area is described by a white circle, which we can see on the map and mini map.

In this area, we will be safe, because outside the area, radioactive storms will take our lives over time.

If we pay attention to safe areas, we often see players fleeing to escape the storm before it is too late.

 This situation is an excellent opportunity to eliminate the opponent."</string>
    <string name="Details5">"Mini maps are very important to avoid a series of threats to our existence.

If you hear gunshots nearby, look for the red triangles on the mini map as they will indicate the origin of the gunshots.

 In this way, you will know that there are enemies nearby.

 At other times, we will hear explosions and vehicles driven by players.

 Both will be marked with yellow or red dots around the mini map.

 This will tell us which direction the sound comes from.

 In addition to radiation, there are hazardous areas.

 These areas are marked as dangerous with red circles.

 In a few seconds, a bomber will destroy that place, so please escape as soon as possible!

 The drone shows the position of the player inside the yellow circle.

Dont expose yourself to other people, but look closer to where the players you find are."</string>
    <string name="Details6">In Free Fire, we have many tools available to be the last survivor, but you must also know how to use them. Through these skills, explore how to become the best Free Fire player.</string>
    <string name="Details7">"These vehicles are used to quickly move to other places, where there are a lot of loot, and can also pass the players we found on the road without players.

If we make too much sound, other players will be able to hear us.

 Therefore, please be careful when using cars, trucks and motorcycles so as not to reveal our location."</string>
    <string name="DiaDetails1">"We will get a gold coin for participation only, so entering the game will always be a good time. If you want to make more money, then practice and hard work is a good thing, because the game will reward survival time, final position, elimination and headshots.

In addition, by playing games, you will be able to complete daily challenges.

There are various challenges, especially if you have purchased an Elite Pass (unlocked with real money only).

After completing the challenge, you will receive one or more explosive medals.

 These tasks are usually to fight for a certain number of minutes, use a specific weapon, achieve a specific number of eliminations, or ultimately stay in a high position.

Explosive medals are used for the Fire Pass. On this site, you'll unlock items as you get more medals.

 If you purchase Elite Pass, you'll get better rewards in the form of gold, diamonds and even skins.

Otherwise, you can limit yourself to the Free Pass, but the rewards will be much scarcer."</string>
    <string name="DiaDetails2">"This is a simple and safe way to make money, but under no circumstances will we get diamonds just for entry. After entering the game, daily rewards will always appear, usually, you will get 350 gold coins every week.

 This is a very simple way to accumulate such virtual funds, so please try to enter Free Fire every day."</string>
    <string name="DiaDetails3">"We provide free boxes in the game store every day.

    To find this box, go to the General section and click on the Daily Quote section.

    There is also the famous Luck Royale, we can access it from the main menu.

    There, we tested our luck.

    However, you can use so-called ordinary vouchers or spend gold coins to participate in the Royal Gold Coin program. If we only use the normal Royal Royal vouchers, the first two rewards that spin every week usually contain 100 gold coins each.

    To purchase these rewards, click on the red bag to the right of the Royal Gold Coin.

    There is also the famous Luck Royale, we can access it from the main menu. There, we tested our luck.

    However, you can use so-called ordinary vouchers or spend gold coins to participate in the Royal Gold Coin program.

        If we only use the normal Royal Royal vouchers, the first two rewards that spin every week usually contain 100 gold coins each.</string>

</resources>